# Colors:
# - Primary and secondary are optional
# - Primary and secondary colors are replaced with color specified in the DNA
# - Primary and secondary should be the exact same color as used in the SVG.
# - Replace-collisions may occur, make sure that all matching color-codes in the SVG are meant to be replaced.
#
# Structure:
#   The category name should match the directory, where all svg files of the category are located in.
#
# `file`: File-name, used to read the SVG file itself. E.g. "Colored Eyes.svg"
# `id`:   The part id, second part. E.g. "colored_eyes"
# `name`: Display name: used in the web-app to display to users. "colored eyes"
#
# IMPORTANT:
# Every name -> id mapping must also be unique,
#  to create consistent queries on the client-side.
#
parts:
  general:
    - back: "Background.svg"
      id: "background"
      name: "background"
      colors:
        "BackgroundColor": "#E6E6E6"
    - back: "Head.svg"
      id: "head"
      name: "head"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
  eyes:
    - back: "Colored Eyes.svg"
      id: "colored_eyes"
      name: "colored eyes"
      colors:
        "Head.Eyes.EyeColor": "#0B4AA8"
    - back: "Ethereum Eyes.svg"
      id: "ethereum_eyes"
      name: "Ethereum eyes"
    - back: "Money Eyes.svg"
      id: "money_eyes"
      name: "$$ eyes"
    - back: "Closed Eyes 2.svg"
      id: "closed_eyes_2"
      name: "closed eyes 2"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Closed Eyes.svg"
      id: "closed_eyes"
      name: "closed eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Crying Eyes 2.svg"
      id: "crying_eyes_2"
      name: "crying eyes 2"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Crying Eyes.svg"
      id: "crying_eyes"
      name: "crying eyes"
    - back: "Half Closed Eyes.svg"
      id: "half_closed_eyes"
      name: "half closed eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Mad Eyes.svg"
      id: "mad_eyes"
      name: "mad eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Red Eyes.svg"
      id: "red_eyes"
      name: "red eyes"
    - back: "Small Eyes.svg"
      id: "small_eyes"
      name: "small eyes"
    - back: "Wide Eyes.svg"
      id: "wide_eyes"
      name: "wide eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Alien Eyes and Nose.svg"
      id: "alien_eyes"
      name: "alien eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Ghandi Pepe.svg"
      id: "ghandi"
      name: "Ghandi"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "Illuminati Eye.svg"
      id: "illuminati_eye"
      name: "illuminati eye"
    - back: "Smug Eyes.svg"
      id: "smug_eyes"
      name: "Smug eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "FutureRobotEyes.svg"
      id: "future_robot_eyes"
      name: "Future Robot eyes"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#3a60ff"
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#2392ff"
    - back: "MonkasEye.svg"
      id: "monkas_eye"
      name: "Monkas Eye"
    - back: "ScaryEyes.svg"
      id: "scary_eyes"
      name: "Scary eyes"
    - back: "WokeEyes.svg"
      id: "woke_eyes"
      name: "Woke eyes"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - back: "LolEyes.svg"
      id: "lol_eyes"
      name: "LOL Eyes"
      colors:
        "Head.Eyes.EyeColor": "#ff0000"
  glasses:
    - front: "SmartGlasses.svg"
      id: "smart_glasses"
      name: "smartglasses"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#CCCCCC"
    - front: "Sunglasses 1.svg"
      id: "sunglasses_1"
      name: "sunglasses 1"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#ff0000"
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#4D4D4D"
    - front: "Sunglasses 2.svg"
      id: "sunglasses_2"
      name: "sunglasses 2"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#1A1A1A"
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#ADADAD"
    - front: "Thug Life Glasses.svg"
      id: "thuglife"
      name: "Thug Life glasses"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#000044"
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#FFFFFF"
    - front: "Pirate.svg"
      id: "pirate_hat"
      name: "pirate_hat"
      colors:
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#666666"
        "Extra.Glasses.SecondaryColor": "#7F0502"
    - front: "ExplosionGoggles.svg"
      id: "explosion_goggles"
      name: "Explosion Goggles"
    - front: "FutureGlasses.svg"
      id: "future_glasses"
      name: "Future glasses"
    - front: "KimJongUnGlasses.svg"
      id: "kim_jong_un_glasses"
      name: "Kim Jong Un glasses"
    - front: "VRSet.svg"
      id: "vr_set"
      name: "VRSet"
  hair:
    - front: "70s Hair.svg"
      id: "70s_hair"
      name: "70s hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Elvis Hair.svg"
      id: "elvis_hair"
      name: "Elvis hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Goku Hair.svg"
      id: "goku_hair"
      name: "Goku hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Modern Hair.svg"
      id: "modern_hair"
      name: "modern hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Nerd Hair.svg"
      id: "nerd_hair"
      name: "nerd hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#78391E"
    - front: "Trump Hair.svg"
      id: "trump_hair"
      name: "Trump hair"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#E4B833"
    - front: "Bitcoin Cap.svg"
      id: "bitcoin_cap"
      name: "Bitcoin cap"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#F99F30"
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#AD661F"
    - front: "Mine Hat.svg"
      id: "mine_hat"
      name: "Miner hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#CCCCCC"
    - front: "Bandana.svg"
      id: "bandana"
      name: "bandana"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Beanie.svg"
      id: "beanie"
      name: "beanie"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#5B3B3B"
    - front: "Hat.svg"
      id: "hat"
      name: "hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#3E4E5C"
    - front: "Hat 2.svg"
      id: "hi_hat"
      name: "High hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#D91F26"
    - front: "Mining Cap.svg"
      id: "mining_cap"
      name: "Mining cap"
    - front: "Mohawk.svg"
      id: "mohawk"
      name: "mohawk"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Mohawk.svg"
      id: "mohawk"
      name: "mohawk"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Terrorist.svg"
      id: "terrorist"
      name: "terrorist"
    - front: "Thug Life Cap.svg"
      id: "thug_life_cap"
      name: "Thug Life cap"
    - front: "Wig.svg"
      id: "wig"
      name: "wig"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "big_bun.svg"
      id: "big_bun"
      name: "big bun"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "bun_beard.svg"
      id: "bun_beard"
      name: "bun & beard"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "cowboy_hat.svg"
      id: "cowboy_hat"
      name: "cowboy hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#ac693c"
        "Head.Hair.HatColor": "#825a5d"
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#00ff00"
    - front: "old_bun.svg"
      id: "old_bun"
      name: "oldschool bun"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#864646"
    - front: "spike_hair.svg"
      id: "spike_hair"
      name: "spikes"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
    - front: "two_braids.svg"
      id: "two_braids"
      name: "double braids"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ffd942"
    - back: "pharaoh_back.svg"
      front: "pharaoh_front.svg"
      id: "pharaoh"
      name: "pharaoh"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#ff0000"
    - front: "Chaplin.svg"
      id: "chaplin"
      name: "Chaplin"
    - front: "EgyptianHat.svg"
      id: "egyptian_hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#437dc0"
        "Head.Hair.HatColor1": "#4353c0"
    - front: "Frankenstein.svg"
      back: "Frankenstein_back.svg"
      id: "frankenstein"
      name: "Frankenstein"
    - front: "IndianHat.svg"
      back: "IndianHat_back.svg"
      id: "indian_hat"
      name: "Indian Hat"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#ffbd35"
        "Head.Hair.HatColor1": "#ff6819"
        "Extra.Glasses.PrimaryColor": "#ffed31"
    - front: "KimJongUnHair.svg"
      id: "kim_jong_un_hair"
      name: "Kim Jong Un Hair"
    - front: "KnifeThroughHead.svg"
      back: "KnifeThroughHead_back.svg"
      id: "knife_through_head"
      name: "Knife Through Head"
    - front: "Mcafee.svg"
      id: "mcafee"
      name: "John McAfee"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#f5e392"
    - front: "MinerHat2.svg"
      id: "minerhat2"
      name: "Miner Hat2"
    - front: "Nakamoto.svg"
      back: "Nakamoto_back.svg"
      id: "nakamoto"
      name: "Nakamoto"
    - front: "Nun.svg"
      back: "Nun_back.svg"
      id: "nun"
      name: "Nun"
    - front: "PaperHat.svg"
      id: "paper_hat"
      name: "Paper Hat"
    - front: "Rollers.svg"
      back: "Rollers_back.svg"
      id: "rollers"
      name: "Rollers"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#8d3d26"
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#eb2626"
    - front: "Samurai.svg"
      back: "Samurai_back.svg"
      id: "samurai"
      name: "Samurai"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HatColor2": "#00f"
    - front: "SombreroHat.svg"
      id: "sombrero_hat"
      name: "Sombrero Hat"
    - front: "TinFoilAntennaHat.svg"
      back: "TinFoilAntennaHat_back.svg"
      id: "tinfoil_antenna_hat"
      name: "Tin Foil Antenna Hat"
    - front: "TurkishHat.svg"
      id: "turkish_hat"
      name: "Turkish Hat"
    - front: "UASFHat.svg"
      back: "UASFHat_back.svg"
      id: "uasf_hat"
      name: "UASFHat"
    - front: "CryptoPepesHat.svg"
      back: "UASFHat_back.svg"
      id: "cpep_uasf_hat"
      name: "CryptoPepes (UASF style)"
    - front: "VikingHat.svg"
      id: "viking_hat"
      name: "Viking Hat"
    - front: "WizardHat.svg"
      id: "wizard_hat"
      name: "Wizard Hat"
    - front: "vitalik_hair_front.svg"
      back: "vitalik_hair_back.svg"
      id: "vitalik_hair"
      name: "Vitalik Hair"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984e"
  mouth:
    - front: "Basic Lips.svg"
      id: "basic_lips"
      name: "basic lips"
    - front: "Cool Smile.svg"
      id: "cool_smile"
      name: "cool smile"
    - front: "Crying Lips.svg"
      id: "crying_lips"
      name: "crying lips"
    - front: "Extreme Sad Lips.svg"
      id: "extreme_sad_lips"
      name: "extreme sad lips"
    - front: "Fake Smile.svg"
      id: "fake_smile"
      name: "fake smile"
    - front: "Happy Lips.svg"
      id: "happy_lips"
      name: "happy lips"
    - front: "Lips to Kiss.svg"
      id: "lips_to_kiss"
      name: "lips to kiss"
    - front: "Mad Lips 2.svg"
      id: "mad_lips_2"
      name: "mad lips 2"
    - front: "Mad Mouth.svg"
      id: "mad_mouth"
      name: "mad mouth"
    - front: "Open Mouth.svg"
      id: "open_mouth"
      name: "open mouth"
    - front: "Sad Lips 2.svg"
      id: "sad_lips_2"
      name: "sad lips 2"
    - front: "Smiling Lips.svg"
      id: "smiling_lips"
      name: "smiling lips"
    - front: "Surprised Mouth.svg"
      id: "surprised_mouth"
      name: "surprised mouth"
    - front: "Tongue Out.svg"
      id: "tongue_out"
      name: "tongue out"
      colors:
        "BackgroundColor": "#E6E6E6"
    - front: "What Mouth.svg"
      id: "what_mouth"
      name: "what mouth"
      colors:
        "BackgroundColor": "#E6E6E6"
    - front: "Wide Mouth.svg"
      id: "wide_mouth"
      name: "wide mouth"
    - front: "Wtf Mouth.svg"
      id: "wtf_mouth"
      name: "WTF mouth"
    - front: "Young Lips.svg"
      id: "young_lips"
      name: "young lips"
    - front: "Smug Lips.svg"
      id: "smug_lips"
      name: "smug lips"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - front: "braces.svg"
      id: "braces"
      name: "braces"
    - front: "rabbit_teeth.svg"
      id: "rabbit_teeth"
      name: "rabbit teeth"
    - front: "bad_ass_mouth.svg"
      id: "bad_ass_mouth"
      name: "bad ass mouth"
      colors:
        "Head.Hair.HairColor": "#ff0000"
# Disabled for now, does not fit well with other parts.
#    - back: "Pacman.svg"
#      id: "pacman"
#      name: "Pacman"
    - front: "SmugMustache.svg"
      id: "smug_mustache"
      name: "Smug Mustache"
    - front: "DrinkCoffee.svg"
      id: "drink_coffee"
      name: "Drink Coffee"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984e"
    - front: "DrinkWine.svg"
      id: "drink_wine"
      name: "Drink Wine"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984e"
    - front: "FeelsBirthday.svg"
      id: "feels_birthday"
      name: "Feels Birthday"
    - front: "OldSadMouth.svg"
      id: "old_sad_mouth"
      name: "Old Sad Mouth"
    - front: "LolMouth.svg"
      id: "lol_mouth"
      name: "LOL Mouth"
  neck:
    - back: "Choker Necklace.svg"
      id: "choker_necklace"
      name: "choker necklace"
    - back: "Dollar Necklace.svg"
      id: "dollar_necklace"
      name: "dollar necklace"
    - back: "Punk Necklace.svg"
      id: "punk_necklace"
      name: "punk necklace"
    - back: "cowboy_neck.svg"
      id: "cowboy_neck"
      name: "cowboy scarf"
  shirt:
    - back: "Basic Shirt.svg"
      id: "basic_shirt"
      name: "basic shirt"
      colors:
        "Body.Shirt.ShirtColor": "#2249FC"
    - back: "Camp Shirt.svg"
      id: "camp_shirt"
      name: "camp shirt"
      colors:
        "Body.Shirt.ShirtColor": "#FFFFFF"
    - back: "Suit and tie.svg"
      id: "suit"
      name: "Suit and tie"
      colors:
        "Body.Shirt.ShirtColor": "#DD0000"
    - back: "Darth Pepe.svg"
      id: "darth_pepe"
      name: "darth pepe"
    - back: "KimJongUnShirt.svg"
      id: "kim_jong_un_shirt"
      name: "Kim Jong Un Shirt"
    - back: "MexicanPoncho.svg"
      id: "mexican_poncho"
      name: "Mexican Poncho"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984E"
    - front: "Pepemon.svg"
      back: "Pepemon_back.svg"
      id: "pepemon"
      name: "Pepemon"
    - front: "Dracula.svg"
      back: "DraculaBack.svg"
      id: "dracula"
      name: "Dracula Suit"
    - back: "vitalik_shirt_back.svg"
      front: "vitalik_shirt_front.svg"
      id: "vitalik_shirt"
      name: "Vitalik Shirt"
      colors:
        "Skin.Color": "#68984e"
